# AHMED NASRULLAH

Sargodha,Pakistan +923407534556 ahmednasrullah77@gmail.com in linkedin.com/in/ahmed-nasrullah-6b6408112/



# Senior Web developer

**Summary** 

**Pro Web developer** with 4 years of experience in structuring, developing and implementing interactive websites, innovative use of technology and SEO to drive traffic and engage users. Able to complete projects effectively and satisfy customers with attractive, user friendly websites.

## Work experience

2018 - Present Senior Web developer

**AWSOL** 

- perform website design and development for clients in diverse fields such as medical, educational and business related.
- work closely with team and learned advanced project management skills.

2014 - 2018 Web developer

Softicks

- work as a full stack web developer
- develop websites for clients
- Manage web projects with 2 -5 web developers.

#### Education

2006 - 2011 Matriculation

connoisseur grammar school

860/1050

2011 - 2013 FSC(Pre-engineering)

Strayer University

798/1100

2014 - 2018 BS(Computer Science)

Strayer University
Graduated with 3.0 CGPA

#### Area of Expertise

- Advanced programming and designing skills
- Landing page development
- Ecommerce websites development
- Strong Collaboration skills
- Website optimization
- Excellent problem solving skills

## Skills

## **Applications**

- XAMPP
- Adobe dreamweaver
- Sublime text
- ATOM
- Brackets
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Visual Studio
- SQL SERVER

## Languages

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- jQuery
- Angular 6
- JSON
- PHP(codeigniter,Laravel)
- Wordpress
- C,C++
- ASP.NET

## **Projects**

- 1. https://www.liq.com/
- 2. https://www.parksleephotels.com/
- 3. http://www.stayparktravel.com/
- 4. http://www.tygervinum.com/
- 5. http://speakshy.com/
- 6. http://www.dcutz.com/HealthCare/